[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
Hey!
It's damn near impossible
to track you down,
Mr. Sarm.
Quickly! Come on!
Hey!
And where exactly are we going?
To the boat, obviously.
Never heard of it?
"The safest place
is often the most dangerous one."
Oh!
Hey! Jam!
Jam!
Jam.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to stay here.
Mr. Sarm!
You are still awake?
The night is far from over.
By the way...
it's almost 2 A.M.
Still not back in your body yet?
I am not the Krasue.
The Krasue.
Oh, the Krasue.
The Krasue, huh?
The Krasue.
Are you...
alright?
Well, I'm officially heartbroken.
I miss Ghibli.
Ghibli?
Ghibli is a pygmy owl
that lives at the bungalow.
It loves coming to see me,
always keeping me company at night.
I haven't seen it in days.
Oh.
Don't tell me to go back to
the bungalow or anything.
I refuse to go back to
either the bungalow or Pak Chong.
How about...
Is there anything you would like to share?
I'm trying to get over it.
I've been goofing around for six months,
and I'm losing my mind.
I only sleep two to three hours a night.
Are you really that heartbroken?
Don't rub it in,
or I'll cry right in front of you.
If you want to get over it,
the first step is accepting the truth.
And how am I not accepting the truth?
Like this.
Do you know
what the last words I said to PiMai were?
"Hap-Pi New Year."
Huh?
I told him...
I wouldn't make him feel uncomfortable.
I'd only see him as a younger brother,
and I wanted him to see me
as just an older brother.
Can I get a round of applause
worthy of a main character?
Louder!
Louder.
Enough.
Who taught you to be so extra?
So, Sib and PiMai
are back together?
Their relationship never really ended.
They just needed some time apart.
I just asked them, actually.
You have a knife?
Just stab me in the heart already.
After six months apart,
they're already in heaven.
People deal with problems
differently, do they not?
Go ahead.
Keep talking.
I want to hear more.
Someday...
you will find someone you love
who loves you back.
That quote...
It's exactly what PiMai said.
I don't think that person exists.
But the boy named Lantao is kind of sweet...
Stop it right there.
Don't.
Don't say that.
Just let him have a bright future.
So you know that
being with you
would only lead to a bleak future.
Jam!
Always taking a dig at me.
Am I not meant for love?
Why did you ask me that?
You just said that
being with me
would only lead to a bleak future.
I was just teasing.
Teasing?
Careful, I might just tease you back.
If there's anything
you'd like to share with me,
feel free, by the way.
I don't like owing anyone anything.
Mr. Sarm...
Mr. Sarm.
Please...
get your act together soon.
Ow!
Whoa...
So heavy...
Well then,
I guess you are sleeping here.
Someday,
you will find someone you love
who loves you back.
[Your Third Series]
♫Still feeling lonely? Well, you've got me,♫
♫Keeping you busy every day♫
♫I might not be the one you wanted,♫
♫But give it time, you'll love me anyway♫
♫It's your heart, so it's your choice,♫
♫I won't ever stand in your way♫
♫But when they make you blue,♫
♫Can you please let me take care of you?♫
♫I'm here to love you as myself,
not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space
when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you,
no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart,
lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ouch...
Ow...
Is he awake?
Sib sent Snoop here just to suffer,
and Snoop willingly took on the task.
That's why we've been on the run like this.
I didn't mean to drag him along with me,
but I can't just leave him out there.
Since we're in the same boat,
we can't just go our separate ways.
At first,
my goal was to make myself
so insufferable that he'd leave.
But honestly,
having Jam here...
isn't that bad.
It's actually the opposite.
Jam is like positive energy with legs.
You are all bark and no bite.
But sometimes, he's so supportive that
I want to support his face with my fist.
Boiled crabs...
What's with him?
I've been alive for 30 years,
and I've never seen anyone
talk about food in their sleep.
That's the spirit,
I guess...
Boiled crabs...
Whoa...
What can I get you, handsome?
Uh...
I'll have five kilos of crabs.
Oh...
Since you want the whole lot...
No problem.
I'll throw in some freebies:
five kilos of shrimp
and five kilos of mantis shrimp, on the house.
If you don't mind, Uncle.
Whoa, you're awesome.
They are for sale.
You might as well
just give them all away.
Then
I'll buy it all.
I'll take everything.
This handsome fellow will pay for it.
As for your trouble with her,
you're on your own, Uncle.
Why are you staring at me?
Or...
am I that handsome?
Young man,
let me take a closer look at you.
Of course.
Are you the same person?
Same person as who?
Oh!
The guy from the soap opera last night.
But you, young man,
are much more handsome.
I knew it!
Whatever you've got,
I'll take it all!
- Okay. Sure thing.
- I'll take it all.
I'll take the ice, too.
No problem.
We'll even cook them
and deliver them to you.
Whoa...
Where are you staying?
Oh, my resort is...
There. Over there.
It's nearby.
Oh.
You're both good-looking and kind-hearted.
All good?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Alright.
Hey.
Who was that just now?
Oh.
Just a customer.
Does he live around here?
He said he's staying nearby.
[Calls]
[Boss]
Mr. Sarm!
Where are you, Mr. Sarm?!
What are you doing over there,
Mr. Sarm?
Yes.
It's me.
I was in search of your boiled crabs.
You think this is funny?
Aw.
Aw, aw, aww...
Little Jam.
I'm right here.
I wasn't gone or anything.
Do not disappear on me again.
Do not act crazy like this,
and do not get yourself hurt.
Always telling me what I can and can't do.
Who do you think you are?
Do I have to listen to you?
Whatever.
No means no.
Okay...
"I won't."
I won't disappear on you.
I won't act crazy like this,
and I won't get myself hurt.
Okay?
Now, stop being a crybaby.
Hey...
Snoop.
I already told you my name is not Snoop.
Oh, did you?
Okay, if that's the case,
mm...
Snug.
I'll call you Snug, then.
Hey.
You're really that worried
I'll disappear on you,
huh?
It is because someone is hunting you down.
If you disappear on me,
where am I supposed to find you?
And...
how did you get to Ko Pha-ngan?
Why could I not find
any travel information at all?
Well,
that's a "secret."
What about you?
How did you find me?
Same answer.
It is a "secret."
Oh...
- Always got to have the last word, huh?
- Ouch!
That hurt.
Hey.
Are you planning on following me forever?
Not exactly.
Mr. Sib has already set the deadline:
Ms. Namnueng's wedding day.
That is only a little over a week away.
You are not really returning?
Your own sister
is getting married, you know.
They can have
their wedding just fine without me.
But...
she wants you there on her special day.
You are really not going home?
Perhaps...
you are not ready to meet Mr. PiMai.
I'm just not ready to get scolded by my dad.
This sucks!
Hey!
Hey...
Good evening,
Mr. Sarm.
Feeling a bit thirsty.
You guys really went through
a lot of trouble, huh?
What the hell do you want?
You're quick to catch on.
Get on the boat with us.
Don't make a fuss.
Sure.
But not tonight.
It's getting late.
Go to bed already.
Go home to your wife and kids.
They're probably missing you.
Also, stop trespassing already.
Next time, I'll call the police.
Hey!
Do you want to do this the easy way,
or the hard way?
Fine.
If you want me that badly,
fine.
Get a palanquin and take me away.
Get me a yogurt drink, too.
No straw?
Are you nuts?!
Take him!
Hey, hey, hey!
You guys are serious?!
Hey!
You are not taking Mr. Sarm anywhere!
Who sent you here?
If you want something, just ask nicely
instead of breaking in at this hour.
I've been searching for him for half a year,
but I couldn't find even a trace of him.
But after you came here,
everything got way easier.
Hey, hey.
- Hey, stop it.
- Be still.
Don't touch him.
It's okay.
That was nothing!
Jam!
This brat!
You.
Let's make you suffer with him, too!
Take them away!
- Hey! Stop!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Be gentle.
- Hey!
- Don't hurt Jam!
- Let me go!
- Stop!
- Jam!
Let go of me!
Hey.
Let's be real here.
Is this a boat or a piece of junk?
Are we even going to make it
to your destination, huh?
I bet it'll sink before we even get there.
We probably won't even make it.
- Pray you make it through the night
- Whoa...
before talking smack.
Wow...
What the hell did I ever do to you?
Did I step on your toes or something?
No.
You didn't do anything to us.
But to someone else?
I'm not so sure.
Oh...
Then at least do us a favor
and give us a few hints.
Who hired you?
You know exactly what you did
and to whom.
Why the hell did you stop the boat, though?
What, are we fishing?
Oh, what,
are you putting on a concert now?
Alright.
Raise your right hand!
♫Devote himself to his master♫
♫Shoot...♫
Shut your mouth.
Keep an eye on them.
I need to talk to the boss.
Understood.
Be sure to look at me.
Am I handsome?
Wow, wow.
Huh?
Jam...
Are you okay?
Feeling seasick?
Are you?
I am just a little dizzy.
Come closer, then.
You are in trouble.
They are going to hurt you.
Don't worry.
No one can touch me.
I'm...
a tiger with nine lives.
It is "a cat with nine lives."
I really do not understand you.
Why do you always
take everything so lightly?
I'm not, Jam.
Look at me.
I'm serious.
I mean it.
Do not get hurt, okay?
That is not allowed.
I know.
My dad's feng shui master
told me
I'd live for over a hundred years,
so don't worry.
I don't die easily.
Do not jinx it.
What?
How dare you say that?
Come on.
Just believe me.
Hey!
What's up?
You two...
It's time.
Is it?
What should we do with this kid?
Hey, hey.
Don't do anything to this kid.
A word of advice:
this is...
one of Sattawat's men.
If anything happens to him,
Sattawat won't let any of you live.
If he doesn't report back to Sattawat
within 24 hours,
Sattawat will surely
scour the earth to find him!
So let him go.
Take me instead.
Do whatever you want with me!
Throw me into a pot.
Turn me into a pizza
or tteokbokki.
Just let this kid go.
Right.
Stick to the original plan.
Yes.
Don't worry, Jam.
Go first.
You have to survive, okay?
No!
- Don't worry about me.
- Let go of him.
This tiger has nine lives.
- Hey!
- I'll be with you soon.
- I'll be right behind you.
- Hey!
Hey, be gentle!
- The kid's this tiny!
- Hey!
Hey!
Hey!!
What the hell did you do?!
Let go of me!
Let me go!
You're all dead!
Sattawat will come for your throat!
And so will I!
Jam...
Thee, any news?
No, Uncle.
Honestly,
I really feel for you, Thee.
You have to work so much harder.
Sarm, oh, Sarm.
He's a grown man,
but he's still acting so irresponsibly.
It's not that bad, Song.
No matter how complicated...
the workload
Sarm left behind was,
I handled it with ease.
It's the opposite, actually.
I'm actually honored
to take care of the empire
you built with
your own blood, sweat, and tears.
But Sarm...
ended up neglecting it so badly.
He's made himself this clear.
Why not consider Thee, Dad?
What are you talking about, Sib?
That said,
what if Sarm actually...
can't handle the work when he comes back?
The word "can't"
isn't in Sarm's dictionary, Song.
There's only...
"I want to do it"
or "I don't want to do it."
Come to think of it, you're right.
Right now,
Sarm is probably off...
being his quirky self somewhere.
Either that, or...
Sarm's probably
falling in love with Ko Pha-ngan.
I have found Mr. Sarm.
On Ko Pha-ngan.
It's too bad, really.
Jam!
Little Jam!
Jam!!
Jam!
Jam...
Jam!!
Jam!
Mr. Sarm...
Yeah.
That's right...
It's me.
A ghost...
What are you talking about?
I'm still alive!
Are you hurt?
Little Jam...
You got stung by a sea urchin.
You find a way to get yourself hurt
every single day.
How did you end up here?
I zoomed over here in a long-tail boat.
Little Jam.
What about...
those guys?
It's a long story.
Worry about yourself first.
Ready?
Is it going to hurt?
Like your heart's about to burst.
Is it that painful?
Mm.
Ready?
If it hurts, pinch my leg.
Mm...
All good?
Ready?
Mm.
Three...
Two...
Done.
See?
It didn't hurt at all.
Here.
Get up.
Come on. Get up already.
We can do this the easy way or the hard way.
Can you get a little lower?
I cannot get up...
So extra.
Such a pain.
Come on. Hop on.
Hold on tight, okay?
Or you'll fall again.
Are we good to go?
Thank you...
Thank who?
Huh?
The forest spirits?
Water spirit?
Or who?
Thank you, Mr. Sarm.
Didn't catch that.
Who were you thanking?
I said, "Thank you, Mr. Sarm!"
Yeah!
That's more like it.
Say it loud and clear
just like when you were
shouting at me back there.
Let's go.
Hold on tight, alright?
You are fated to suffer
the same misfortune as your parents.
Jam!
Hey!
Still being stubborn?
You're too weak right now.
Where do you think you're going?
You might fall into the ocean again.
This time,
no one will be there to save you.
You are being so dramatic.
Where are we, anyway?
Well...
we're on some beach on Ko Samui.
- Ko Samui?
- Mm.
And whose house is this?
You're pretty observant.
Well...
I was too lazy to go into town,
so I asked some locals
if I could stay here for the night.
This is the place they gave me.
Oh...
Mm.
Are you hungry?
Come.
Come on.
You can hold my hand.
I won't charge you.
Mm.
Come.
Ow!
Help her out.
Auntie, let me help you.
It's okay, dear.
How are you?
Thank you.
Feeling better?
A whole lot better now.
Has your fever gone down?
Thank you.
Eat up, dear.
I'm back!
- He's drunk...
- Oh!
- Good evening.
- Right.
- Now, now.
- Good evening.
Let's have dinner
so you can take your pills.
How are you feeling?
Little one, has your fever gone down?
A whole lot better now, Uncle.
If you're not better,
come enjoy a drink with me.
A sip or two
will surely make it go away!
- Now, now.
- Alright.
- Let's have dinner.
- Alright, alright.
You always
invite everyone you meet to drink.
- Let's have dinner.
- Right, right, right.
- Let us eat.
- Right?
Whoa...
Here.
- Sweet, right?
- Let me show you how it's done.
Eyes on me.
Watch and learn.
Like this.
Gently pry it upward.
Don't touch the bones.
Alright. Dig in.
Try it.
Go on.
It was hot.
I did not notice the bones.
Hey...
A true warrior is bound to have a few scars.
You have to watch out for the bones, too.
What if you choke on them?
What?
This is how I eat, alright?
Does "Jiranat" mean
"burden" or something?
Hm?
And does "Traiphop"
mean "snarky"?
I never wanted to be a burden to you.
Young man,
what made you so foul-mouthed?
Jam, don't mind him.
As the old saying goes,
"The more a dog barks,
the more it loves its owner."
Try it. It's tasty.
Try the fish with this.
Since last night...
Mr. Sarm has been acting strange.
He still talks the same as always,
but his eyes...
somehow look sadder.
Oh.
It's late.
Why are you still up?
I am waiting for you...
Oh...
I mean, I have been waiting for you
to get in here
so I can close the mosquito net.
You're right.
Can we sleep with the lights on?
Oh...
It's so bright...
You might get a migraine.
We don't have any medicine either.
I understand.
We can turn them off, then.
Mr. Sarm.
What?
You seem stressed.
Based on what?
Well...
you were frowning the whole time.
Oh.
Hey,
did you know that
a man who frowns
like this
looks badass?
Like... it makes him look cool.
Cool, you know?
Not true.
You are being evasive.
Hey.
What are you fussing about?
Hm? Tell me.
You are the one acting strange.
What has gotten into you?
Why will you not tell me?
If I told you,
you'd think I was cringe.
You already are.
Let's sleep.
I refuse.
Sleep. Now.
No.
I told you, it's nothing.
You are lying.
Sleep!
I refuse.
Okay.
You need me to lull you to sleep first,
don't you?
Fine.
Want me to sing, too?
Want me to pat your bum, too?
Hush now.
Sleep tight.
Go to sleep.
Stop it.
Why?
This will make you sleep.
Go to sleep. Hush now.
Enough already.
Damn it!
The kitten is being needy!
How is it?
Can you see clearly now?
Mm.
What's this?
Fat...
fingers.
And what about this?
A heart.
It's actually my own heart.
Did you have trouble sleeping last night?
♫I only wish you nothing but the best♫
♫Hoping your smile will never fade♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side♫
Do you want to get a haircut?
Hey...
What doesn't your backpack have? Hm?
It contains everything
based on the concept:
"My backpack has things
that others do not have."
Can you give me a haircut, then?
This house has no mirrors.
Let me help you with that.
I can trust you, right?
Be sure to stay still, then.
Alright.
Make me look handsome.
But it's hard to get
any more handsome than this.
Oh... It's a powerful one, too?
All done.
How do I look?
Do I look handsome enough now?
No, no, no.
Don't let your heart melt just yet,
for this...
is only the beginning.
I'm going squid fishing with Uncle Keua.
You'll be okay here, right?
Mm...
Why would I not be?
Then I'll only be away physically, okay?
[Mission: Hunt Down the Teeny-tiny Tiger]
I used to think that...
my mission was simply to find Mr. Sarm.
Today...
I finally found him.
What's harder now...
is making him believe that
he no longer has to run away
from his past,
his pain,
or those hunting him down.
From now on...
I shall remain by his side
until he finds the courage...
to face everything once more.
We've been through so much together,
so how about we become friends?
I've decided.
We're going back to Ko Pha-ngan tomorrow.
I think I am going to head back.
I want you to come with me.
Will we get to see each other again?
You'll want to see me again, of course.
And you'll miss me a lot, too.
♫It seems like something's moving♫
♫What's in my heart isn't too much, but I only♫
♫I only wish you nothing but the best♫
♫Hoping your smile will never fade♫
♫That's all, for I don't wish
to take someone's place♫
♫I'll simply be right here, always within reach♫
♫Like a gentle breeze bringing you peace♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side, always♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side♫
[Your Third Series]